underarmour.com 2010-06-27

# Under Armour ®

Security & Privacy Policy 

When was this Privacy Statement Last Updated? 

Last revised: January 26, 2010

What is your Privacy Statement? 

**Privacy statement:**

To help us achieve our goal of providing the highest quality products and services, we use information from our interactions with you and other customers, as well as information from certain third parties. Because we respect your privacy, we have procedures to ensure that your personal information is handled in a responsible manner. We have posted this Privacy Statement on our website to let you know what kind of information we collect, the purposes for which we collect and use the information, how it is handled, with whom it may be shared, and what choices you have regarding our use of your information.

As we continue to develop our website and take advantage of advances in technology, our Privacy Statement may change. Please refer to this page frequently for the most up-to-date information.

What are your Security and Privacy policies? 

**Secure ordering:**

We go to great lengths to protect your personal information. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), the industry-standard encryption technology that ensures safe internet transmission of your personal information. When the letters "http" in the URL change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing SSL; also, your browser may give a pop-up message stating that you're about to enter or leave a secure area. Using a browser that is SSL capable will ensure that your information is encoded/encrypted when it is sent over the internet. Our website has also earned a digital certificate from thawte, Inc. When you see thawte's logo on our secure checkout pages, be assured that your information is being transmitted to our secure servers. Ultimately your account and personal information is protected by the password you provided when you created your [www.UnderArmour.com](http://www.underarmour.com/) account. Always keep this password and login information private, and never share it with anyone. Also, remember to sign off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or an Internet café.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet and no data storage can be 100% secure. Consequently, while we endeavor to safeguard your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, we do not warrant or guarantee the absolute security of any personal information you transmit to, from or through our website. We will notify you in the event we become aware of a security breach involving your personal information stored by or for us. By disclosing your email address to us for any reason, you expressly consent to receive electronic notice from us in the event of such a security breach.

**Registration policies:**

To make online shopping faster and easier, you may register with [www.UnderArmour.com](http://www.underarmour.com/). Using your email address and a password of your choice, you may access your account online at any time to add, delete or change information retained in your account.

If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to close your browser at the conclusion of your session. Your information will still be stored with us but it will not be accessible to anyone else from that computer.

We encourage users to create a registered account on our website. The benefit of having a registered account on Underarmour.com is having the ability to view past orders, and quickly access your shipping and billing information with a username and password. When you register with us as an online customer, we may ask for additional information such as what sports you play.

The alternative to having a registered account is being a "Guest" visitor. As a "Guest," you do not have access to past orders, or the benefit of storing your billing and shipping information on our site.

Unfortunately, we do not offer account registration at this time for International Consumers.

What types of personal information does Under Armour gather? 

**Information You Submit to Us:** we receive and store any information you submit on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our features. By usage of our website or through registration thereon, you grant us the permission to process your personal data that has been provided to us via the Under Armour website in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Statement. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as processing your order, responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our website, and communicating with you.

Should you decide to register an account with the Under Armour website, personal data that we will collect, store and use are the following: name and email address. Additionally, you have the option of providing your gender, birth date, sports interests, shipping/billing address, daytime phone number, size and team number.

Should you place an order, personal data that we will collect, store and use are the following: name, billing address, shipping address, credit card number and expiration date, email address and phone number.

**Automatic Information:** when you visit our website, we receive and store certain types of information through automatic data collection tools including cookies, pixel tags, Web beacons, embedded Web links and other commonly used information gathering tools (“Automatic Data Collection Tools”). These Automatic Data Collection Tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website such as your browser type and language, access times, IP address, user-agent string and click stream behavior (i.e., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions that you take in connection with the Under Armour Website). Please see below for more information about our use of cookies and pixel tags.

**Information from Other Sources:** if you have registered an account with us or placed an order through our website, to help us customize shopping for you, improve our communication with you, and improve our business overall, we may obtain certain demographic information about you from reputable third party sources such as Merkle Inc. For example, in the event we determine that you live in a geographical area where the climate is usually cold and you have subscribed to receive email communications from us, we would be more likely to send you communications highlighting our ColdGear® product line rather than our HeatGear® product line.

For what purposes do we collect your personal information? 

**Purposes of use:** We use the information that you provide to us via our website only for the following purposes: processing and fulfilling your order, responding to your requests and your product inquiries, for our own direct marketing purposes, customizing future shopping for you, improving our website, communicating with you and for our own financial accounting purposes. Credit card information is used only for payment processing and fraud prevention.

**Order placement:** Once you decide to place an order, if you are not a registered customer, you will be given the option to register an account with the Under Armour website or to place an order as a Guest only. If you choose to become a registered customer, your personal information will be saved on our system to facilitate your future purchases on our website. Also, as a registered customer, you will have the ability to view your order history on our website. On the other hand, if you choose to place the order as a Guest only, none of your personal information will be saved by us upon completion of your order except as may be reasonably necessary to document our business activities or as needed for required disclosures. Please see the paragraph “What are your security and registration policies?” above for more information about your options to place an order as a registered customer or as a Guest.

**Email communications:** to help us make email communication more useful and interesting, we may receive a confirmation when you open email messages from [www.UnderArmour.com](http://www.underarmour.com/) if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive email messages or other mail from us, please see the paragraph on “Direct marketing” below.

**Direct marketing:** Each registered customer has the choice of receiving announcements about our products and special events or promotions from us via email. You will receive promotional email messages from us only if you have agreed to receive them by (i) clicking in the box next to “Keep me in the loop for Under Armour news and promotions” when entering your shipping and billing information to place an order or when registering, or (ii) clicking on “Get email updates” at the top of the website home page and entering your email address.. Additionally, each time you receive an email message from Under Armour, you will be given the opportunity to no longer receive email communication from Under Armour and to unsubscribe from our mailing list. If you choose to unsubscribe, we will stop sending you email messages. Please note, however, that some email promotions are prepared well in advance. We appreciate your patience in giving us time to carry out your request. You may unsubscribe by selecting the link, "UNSUBSCRIBE" at the bottom of any Under Armour email message. If you would like more information about online marketing practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by our third party service providers, please click <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>.

For what Purpose do you collect pixel tags and cookies? 

**Purposes for which pixel tags and cookies are used:** We use pixel tags and cookies to customize our web pages based upon purchases a visitor has made, to track (in the aggregate and not in terms of individual site visitors) the number of visitors to the site, the paths to the site, activity on the website and purchases, to enable interaction of our website with visitors for purposes such as adding items to a customer’s shopping cart, and to tailor advertisements which appear on other sites a visitor may visit to a visitor’s Web preferences and usage patterns. For additional information about pixel tags and cookies the ways in which we use them, please see the paragraphs **“What are pixel tags and how does Under Armour use them” and “What are cookies and how does Under Armour use them”** below.

What are Pixel Tags and how does Under Armour use them? 

We use "pixel tags," (also known as “tracking pixels” or “web beacons”) which are small graphic files that allow us to monitor the use of our website. The use of pixel tags is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. A pixel tag can collect information such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the tag appears; the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the page on which the pixel tag appears; the time the page containing the pixel tag was viewed; the type of browser that fetched the pixel tag; and the identification number of any cookie (please see “What are Cookies and how does Under Armour use them?" below) on the computer previously placed by that server. When corresponding with you via HTML capable email, we may use "format sensing" technology, which allows pixel tags to let us know whether you received and opened our email. One of ways in which we use pixel tags is through a third-party service provider to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect anonymous (other than the IP address of your computer) information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use this information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements for goods and services. If you would like more information about online marketing practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by our third party service provider, please click <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>.

What are Cookies and how does Under Armour use them? 

A "cookie" is a small data file stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. It allows us to recognize your computer (but not specifically who is using it) when you enter our site by associating the identification numbers in the cookie with other customer information you have provided us. That customer information is stored on our secured database.

We use cookies to identify the pages you click on during your visit to our site and the name of the website you visited immediately before navigating to Underarmour.com. We use this information to improve our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions.

We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and collect information on our behalf or provide services such as credit card processing, shipping, promotional services or data management.

We may also use single pixel images on our website. This technology tells us more about browsing and buying activity within Underarmour.com but none of your personal information (name, address, email address, payment information, etc.) will be received or shared with our third party service providers.

The use of cookies is a standard internet practice and most major websites use them. When shopping on Underarmour.com, cookies allow us to manage the contents of your cart.

Please note:

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you turn off cookies, though, you will not be able to make a purchase from our website.

A note to our customers using Internet Explorer 6.0: 

If you are using Internet Explorer 6.0 and are having difficulty purchasing from our website, please check your privacy settings in your browser and set them to "Medium." If you do not wish to change your privacy settings to "Medium" and you are currently using the "Medium High" or "High" settings, you may choose to override your current cookie handling practices for individual websites that you specify.

With whom does Under Armour share the personal information it receives from me? 

Information about our customers is an important part of our business and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below.

**Third Party Service Providers:** We employ other companies (including our affiliates) and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance (including on-line advertising), providing search results and links, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. These third party service providers have access to customer personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any purpose other than the function which we have directed them to perform on our behalf. We require such third party service providers to implement and maintain reasonable security measures to safeguard the confidentiality, security and integrity of your personal information.

**Protection of Under Armour and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of our company, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in a way that is contrary to the commitments made in this Privacy Statement.

**Merger, Acquisition, Sale/Transfer of Assets or Business:** If our company is acquired by or merged with or into another entity, or if our assets or business is sold or transferred to another entity, your personal information may be transferred to such entity as part of the transaction, and that entity and its affiliates may use your personal information under the terms of their own privacy policies which may differ from this privacy statement.

**With your consent:** other than as described above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. This includes sharing your personal information with an unaffiliated third party for such third party’s direct marketing use. We will not share your personal information for this purpose without your prior consent.

What choices do I have about accessing and updating my personal information? 

If you are a registered customer, you may access your account by visiting the "My Account" section of our website. From this link, you can view, update or delete certain of your personal information from our database. Please note that we reserve the right to retain personal information relating to you for a period of time as is reasonably necessary to document our business activities or as needed for required disclosures. If you wish to edit personal information but are unable to do so by visiting the “My Account” section of our website, please click [http://www.underarmour.com/shop/us/en/customer-service#contact_us](http://www.underarmour.com/shop/us/en/customer-service#contact%3Ci%3Eus). If you are not a registered customer but wish to contact us about accessing any personal information retained by us, please click [http://www.underarmour.com/shop/us/en/customer-service#contactus](http://www.underarmour.com/shop/us/en/customer-service#contact_us).

How may I contact Under Armour about my personal information? 

What are your Registration and E-mail Subscription policies? 

To make online shopping faster and easier, you may register with UnderArmour.com. Using your email address and a password of your choice, you may access your account online at any time to add, delete or change information.

If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to close your browser at the conclusion of your session. Your information will still be stored with us but it will not be accessible to anyone else from that computer.

We encourage users to create a registered account on our website. The benefit of having a registered account on Underarmour.com is having the ability to track shipments, view past orders, and quickly access your shipping and billing information with a username and password. When you register with us as an online customer, we may ask for additional information such as what sports you play.

The alternative to having a registered account is being a "Guest" visitor. As a "Guest," you do not have access to tracking, past orders, or the benefit of storing your billing and shipping information on our site.

**Emails:**

Each registered user has the choice of receiving announcements and promotions from Underarmour.com via email. You will receive promotional emails from us only if you have asked to receive them. Each time you receive an email from Under Armour, you will be given the opportunity to "opt-out," or stop receiving them. If you choose to "opt-out," we will stop sending you emails. Please note, however, that some email promotions are prepared well in advance. We appreciate your patience in giving us time to carry out your request. You may "opt-out" by selecting the link, "OPT-OUT OF MAILING LIST" at the bottom of any Under Armour email.

Under Armour does not sell its mailing list or customers' email addresses.

Links to Third Party Websites: 

Our website may contain links to certain third-party websites. Under Armour does not own, control or operate such linked sites, and is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such linked sites. Privacy policies and practices for such linked sites may differ from our privacy statement and practices. Your access and use of such linked sites is entirely and solely at your own risk. We urge you to read the privacy policies of such linked sites before disclosing your personal information on such sites.

Changes to this Privacy Statement: 

We may update this privacy statement from time to time without prior notice. You can determine when this statement was last revised by referring to the “Last revised” legend at the top of this page. Any changes to our statement will become effective upon posting of the revised statement on the Internet, accessible through [www.UnderArmour.com](http://www.underarmour.com/). We encourage you to bookmark this page and to periodically review it to ensure familiarity with the most current version of our privacy statement. If you are a registered customer, we may notify you of any changes to this privacy statement via email and may ask you to affirmatively acknowledge consent to the changes (e.g., by checking a box or clicking a button) at the time of your next account login on our website.

Special Note to Parents: 

Under Armour, Inc. takes the privacy of children seriously. Our site is not directed at children, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through our website and we request that children under the age of 13 not submit any personal information through our website.

Notice To California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights: 

Effective January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (known as the “Shine the Light” law) requires that if a business has an established business relationship with a California resident and has within the immediately preceding calendar year disclosed such resident’s personal information to a third party, knowing or having reason to know that such third party used the information for its direct marketing purposes, then the business must disclose such information-sharing to the resident upon request, including what personal information was shared, and with whom it was shared. A business is deemed in compliance with this law if: (1) it has a published privacy policy of not sharing a customer’s personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes without the customer’s consent (either opt-in or opt-out); and (2) it provides the customer upon request with a notice of his/her choice to prevent such sharing and a cost-free means to exercise that choice. As a general matter, consent by “opt-in” means that a business will not share a customer’s personal information with third parties for their direct marketing use, unless the customer affirmatively consents to such sharing (e.g., by checking a box or clicking on a button to manifest consent). On the other hand, consent by “opt-out” means that a business may share a customer’s personal information with third parties for their direct marketing use, unless the customer expressly disallows or objects to such sharing (e.g., by checking a box or clicking on a button to manifest disallowance or objection).

As stated above, Under Armour does not disclose your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, unless with your affirmative consent (i.e., “opt-in”). California residents may request an information-sharing disclosure from us by emailing your request to [CustomerService@UnderArmour.com](mailto:CustomerService@UnderArmour.com) . Please note that, under the law, we are not required to respond to your request more than once in a calendar year, nor are we required to respond to any requests that are not sent to the above-designated email address.

What other languages is your privacy policy translated to?
